Prophet T.B. Joshua sent the New Morning Water to be ministered by his evangelists
to the congregation in the name of Jesus Christ.
As the ministration began, miracles, signs and wonders broke out among the people
as God's mighty power touched them - spirit, soul and body.
Watch as this man receives the New Morning Water and comes under the delivering influence of the Holy Spirit.
Suddenly, he begins to cough and vomit out poisonous substances,
and the spiritual cause of his problem is uprooted as he vomits out several needles.
Take note, these are no ordinary needles the man is vomiting out but it is part of his deliverance
from the hands of darkness, which has been using him as an agent of destruction.
Here you can clearly see some of the needles the man vomited out on the floor
after the ministration of the New Morning Water in the name of Jesus Christ.
Let us hear the confession of the evil spirit
and how it had used these spiritual needles, and how it had affected this man's life.
To God be the Glory. As you can watch on the television screen,
needles are coming out of the system of a human being upon the ministration of the New Morning Water.
So right now we want to hear from the brother - how come these pins and needles ended up in his system.
I'm a python.
Okay, what are these pins for?
They are very dangerous for the human body.
Ministration Of The New Morning Water In Jesus' Name
Who are you? Speak out!
Who are you? What have you done to this body? Who are you evil spirit? Who are you?
They are very dangerous for the human body.
How are they dangerous?
When I meet a woman without a condom ---
So what do you do with that woman when you meet her? What happens to her?
They begin to destroy so many things internally.
What have you destroyed? How many people have you destroyed?
They are many.
And how did you destroy this man? How did you destroy him?
These needles will turn into maggots inside their stomachs.
What have you done to him?
They will turn into maggots inside the stomach.
And how did these pins enter his body? How did they enter the body? What are these pins are for?
Needles Vomited After Ministration Of The New Morning Water In Jesus' Name
They are for destruction.
For destruction, and how do you use these pins to destroy?
If I meet a woman without a condom, they will turn into maggots inside her stomach and start eating.
How many women have you destroyed with these needles?
How many women?
I cannot know. I can't count.
Uncountable. Alright.
Lord Jesus Christ, this is your power, this is your glory.
This is your power, this is your glory, in the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus, come out of this body! Out!
Come out, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Now free in Jesus name, through the medium of the New Morning Water
sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua, in Jesus' name!
Needles Vomited After Ministration Of The New Morning Water In Jesus' Name
Rise up, brother, you're free!
Set Free through The Ministration Of The New Morning Water In Jesus' Name
Okay, brother, how are you?
I'm fine.
OK, can you look on the floor?
Can you look on the floor? What do you see on the floor? Here? What do you see?
Set Free through The Ministration Of The New Morning Water In Jesus' Name
What do you see here on the floor?
They are pins.
These are needles. Where do these needles come from?
I don't know.
But they came from your body!
How come?
Mr. Victor Awuzie, who had vomited the needles during the ministration of the New Morning Water,
met Prophet T.B. Joshua after the service and received his final deliverance in the name of Jesus Christ.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
This was the moment when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for Mr. Victor in the name of Jesus Christ.
Instantly the evil spirit reacts under the delivering power of God.
The evil spirit makes Mr.Victor flail about and tug at his shirt and vest,
desperately trying to resist and escape the fire of God's presence.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
As the deliverance continued, Mr. Victor began urinating
as the Lord Jesus Christ purged his body of any evil thing satan had planted in his life
and the poisonous substances kept pouring out,
until finally he was free completely in the name of Jesus Christ!
Hallelujah.
Urinating Poisonous Substances
Set Free In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mr Victor Uche Awuzie.
I come from Imo state. I'm based in Abuja.
This is my wife, and these are my children.
I was initiated when I was very young, looking for power to have money.
Friends took me somewhere to do something to get money.
They confused me. They didn't tell me the after-effects.
We went to see a native doctor from India who told us to buy a white cock without blemish.
We saved money to bring it. After buying the cock, they took us to a deep forest.
When we got there, we saw a big tree with leaves.
He did some incantations and hit the cock at the center of the tree and the tree opened.
We entered inside the tree and then it closed.
It was a great surprise; it looked like another big world.
I saw a big python and different kind of snakes.
One of them rushed to me and curled itself around my body, from my leg to my head.
It brought its mouth in front of mine.
I was fed from mouth to mouth by the python.
What I was seeing was not the same as what my friends were seeing.
We spent seven days there.
After seven days, the man came back and did another incantation.
The tree opened and we came out.
Ok, so during the seven days you were inside this tree.
What were the things that were inserted into your body?
During the seven days we were inside, it was feeding me from mouth to mouth.
It was putting certain things like needles in my mouth.
The needles were four.
I realized there were four needles as each time one of them entered my stomach, I would feel it.
I felt it four times - that was how I knew that they were four needles.
These needles represented the powers that were being given to you by satan through this initiation.
Yes, the needles were the powers given to me to destroy women.
When I came out, I became an agent to destroy women, both single and married.
There was power in my eyes.
Whenever I looked at any woman, she would fall for me until I finished my mission.
My mission was that when I had sex with any woman,
immediately I released inside the woman,
one needle would go inside and turn into maggots.
It would destroy the woman through fibroids, barrenness, vaginal discharges and other things.
Just give us an example sir, for example,
a married woman that you were able to trap and sleep with,
what would then happen to their marriage after you met them?
We would cause confusion in her marriage through barrenness.
Any woman who cannot have children would not be happy.
The family would not be in unity; it would lead to separation or a big problem in the family.
Explain to us, sir, how would you go about meeting these women?
Where would you find them and what tricks would you use to entice and seduce them?
I used my eyes - whenever I focused on any woman, she would fall for me.
Or, in the night bus, any woman who sat behind me would fall for me that night.
If she was a married woman, she would call her husband to tell him,
"Our vehicle broke down on the way; I cannot make it.
They said they will bring another bus tomorrow".
I would keep her until I finished my mission.
If there was a rich man moving around, if I picked him up and he had anything with him,
mark that date - he would go down; his business and family would go down.
Can you give us an idea of how many women you have actually initiated through these means?
May God forgive me. It was uncountable.
Okay, we're listening to the confession of our brother.
He's explaining how he was initiated at a very young age,
in a quest for power to get money.
The assignment he was given from this demonic kingdom was to destroy women.
Especially married women. To destroy marriages and any woman that he would meet and sleep with,
the needles that were inside his body as given by that python,
that demonic python would actually enter the woman's body as maggots and cause sickness,
cause fibroid, barrenness, vaginal discharge and other ailments
that would eventually cause the end of the marriage or that person would be barren perpetually.
Our brother said that this spirit has pushed him to do this to literally countless numbers of women.
Could you just tell us, while all that was happening to you, you mentioned earlier that you were married?
How did you manage to meet your wife and marry and have children in the midst of this?
We had a covenant that they would not kill my wife.
The only thing was that my wife would suffer and deliver all her children through operation.
That was how it was.
So you mean to say that the three children your wife had,
all of them were delivered through operations and she suffered for it.
So once again, we're hearing the confession of our brother here.
Brother, you mentioned earlier that when you were lured into this cult that you were initiated in,
you never realized the repercussions, the negative consequences that would later happen
as you were being used by satan to destroy women.
What began to happen to your life?
The negative effects that you began to see in your own life in the midst of this?
I lived a very miserable life. They really tormented me - there was no peace in my life.
There was no peace at all.
I'm an artist. I'm a singer.
As I destroyed other people, they also destroyed me.
All my equipment, which I bought for over 800,000 naira -
they broke into my shop and packed all of it.
I don't have anything to say; I only ask God to forgive and restore me.
I'm a gospel artist.
You said that in the midst of this, as satan used you to destroy,
your own life was being destroyed, you went into gospel music,
started singing gospel music. What happened to your career in the area of gospel music?
I made an album but there was no way to move.
We can understand exactly what our brother is saying.
Everything satan promised to give him through this initiation,
at the end of the day it was stolen and taken from him, leaving him even worse than before.
Brother, there's an area we just want to ask you,
you mentioned that you had power in your eyes to seduce women -
once you fixed your eyes, they would fall for you.
Could you explain, was this every single woman you met or were there ---
Have you had some encounters in the past where you tried to seduce a woman and you were unable to
and what happened in that circumstance?
There are real women of God and real children of God.
We used to experience this.
When we would meet people like Prophet T.B. Joshua of The SCOAN,
people under him could never fall like that.
We want you to explain why this is so? What is the reason for that?
Because you know, we have many gods, pastors and prophets but there is 'the last bus stop'.
This is the last bus stop.
We have Adjawadi. We have Adjawadi last bus stop.
When a vehicle takes you to Adjawadi, it must get to the last bus stop.
When it gets to the last stop, it is to turn back.
So this is the last bus stop.
As far as I'm concerned, it is the last bus stop.
I had been to many places but was never delivered until last Sunday when I came here.
If somebody had told me that something like this would happen, I would not have come here;
I would never step my feet here.
But I thank God for that was how God wanted it to be.
Upon whatever happened, I thank God. Glory be to God!
Tell us your experience of last week, sir.
What happened as the New Morning Water was ministered to you in the congregation?
Last week, I came to the service. I was downstairs at the back with my helper and some other men.
When they started ministering the New Morning Water, I was in a haste - I wanted to go,
I told the lady that I wanted to go.
An elderly man told me to be patient but I insisted that I wanted to go out and I didn't want to stay.
I didn't know that something was about to happen.
When they got to that place, it was the first time I ever flew up and fell down.
I didn't even know where I was.
When I stood up, I was very surprised to see myself sitting down.
I looked around, looking at people and I was confused - I didn't know what was going on.
I started vomiting needles - four big needles.
These were not pins, these were needles - four big needles.
I had been suffering from them for a long time.
All parts of my body - my stomach, my private part, chest and head - were painful.
I had been to many hospitals but there was no solution.
We saw that immediately after this encounter after the service,
Prophet T.B. Joshua then prayed for you, and again that spirit burst out of you.
Can you explain what happened when the Prophet prayed for you after the service?
From here, I thought it was over.
Later on, in the evening, when Prophet T.B. Joshua came out, he looked at me
and I said within me, "Another one".
He just waved his hand like this and I wanted to run away.
When I looked at my back, I couldn't run.
He just looked at me and said, "Something is still inside this stomach", and tapped me with power.
That was how I fell, started vomiting and passing urine.
After urinating, I drank nine bottles of water.
The following day, I drank eight bottles of water.
On the third day, I took seven bottles of water.
So, what you were trying to say is that,
immediately after the deliverance, all of those evil powers were leaving your body.
Now tell us, sir, ever since this encounter with Jesus last week,
through the New Morning Water and the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
What are the changes you've seen in your life, as you're here right now.
I don't know why I am sitting down. I am very healthy within me - I can even carry my wife up.
I'm not supposed to sit down because I am fit.
I am very healthy - I have not felt pain anymore.
From head to toe, I am okay.
You mean you're no longer having encounters with that kingdom?
There are no bad dreams again. I'm okay.
Amen! People of God, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Indeed, it is only the power of God that could deliver our brother in such an incredible way.
Finally, what is your word of advice to our viewers all over the world in light of your experiences in life?
My brother, young ones, ladies and boys, married men and women,
if anybody says they want to take you somewhere,
try to find out the implications because they will not tell you.
I want to advise the married ones.
Whether you offend your wife or your wife offends you, make sure you make peace.
Because leaving her with that anger and going out was how we manipulated women.
When your wife is not happy with you, it is very easy.
Whether your wife offended you or you offended your wife,
say, "Honey, I am sorry. Please forget what was going on", so that her anger will calm down.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We listened to that word of advice from our brother.
He's really speaking from experience, from the kingdom of darkness.
This really confirms Prophet T.B. Joshua's sermons,
concerning the need for us to let go off offence
because that truly is an instrument that the devil is using to cause separation,
to cause chaos, to cause problems. Especially in the house and the homes.
We thank God Almighty. Let's just hear one quick word from your wife to round off this wonderful testimony.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Maria Awuzie.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I have four children; they are all here.
All he said - I agree with it because when we got married, there was no peace.
But before then, I saw him like any other person who wanted to marry a woman
and I agreed to get married to him.
After that, we went for court marriage.
After that, he broke the wedding ring and threw it away.
After that, when we slept, I noticed that his legs were chilled like ice cubes.
At around 12 - 3 am, I would touch his legs in a way he would not know and begin to pray,
interceding for him, asking God if it was a sin, may God forgive him.
From all his character, deeds, offence towards others and doing so many evil things,
I reached the conclusion that he was into evil and he might serve an Idol.
So, that's when your eyes opened, to realize that your husband was under the influence of these evil spirits.
Yes.
Now to the glory of God, last week he was delivered.
Can you just tell us, ever since his deliverance, what are the changes you've seen in his life?
What I have seen after his deliverance is that he is always happy with me,
he does not nag anymore and he does not shout at us anymore.
Before, just as you saw him roaring on television,
that was how he would roar at us at home and even in public places.
But now, he is no more like that.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Indeed, that is the evidence of deliverance that the evil spirit has left the life of her husband
and that's how peace and love have been restored to this home, and we give all the glory to God!
Finally, madam, what is your own word of advice?
My own word of advice is especially to women who want to marry.
I am advising you all not to marry any man you just meet on the street or anywhere,
or even at the man's parents home, without inquiring from God Almighty
because it's only God who can give you the best husband.
To men, I advise you before you give your attention to anyone,
you have to inquire from God.
When Ahithophel was against David, David inquired from God and God fought for David.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We thank God for the deliverance in the life of this family.
We know that as they go forth now and make the Word of God the standard for their lives,
definitely the best is yet to come.
As satan used our brother in the past to kill and destroy in so many ways,
we believe his testimony and confession will bring life and deliverance to many people in the same way
and we give glory to God that he's freed from his past. His past is over and the best is yet to come.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Victor Uche Awuzie, I am from Imo state.
The people beside me are my family - my wife and my children.
I really thank God for changing my life and delivering me from my bondage
because I was in bondage.
I thank God for delivering me. Thank You, Jesus!
Since God delivered me, there are many changes.
Formerly, I was not a human being at all.
Physically, I was a human being but spiritually, I was not a human being.
Since He delivered me, I can call myself a human being by doing something that people like.
Since that day, I am seeing changes in my life.
To God be the glory! We thank Jesus Christ for this incredible deliverance.
On behalf of Prophet T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel TV partners,
they're going to support you with the sum of 200,000 naira to start your new life in Christ Jesus,
to support your family and to support your career as well.
Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I really thank you.
Through the Almighty God, this money will enable me to forward my career as a Gospel Artist.
I know what to do with this money.
The Almighty God who provided this money through Pastor T.B. Joshua will give me the wisdom
to utilize this money, so that in a short time, I will come back and give another testimony,
in Jesus' name.
To God be the glory. We thank Jesus Christ for your life!
Better is not good enough, the best is yet to come for you and your family, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank You, Jesus. Thank You. Emmanuel! Thank You, Jesus.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)